listal.com 2019-12-31

# Listal - List the stuff you love! Movies, TV, music, games and books

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Service](https://www.listal.com/help/tos), or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Listal is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Listal will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## INFORMATION GATHERING AND USAGE

  * When you register for Listal we ask for information such as your name and email address
  * Listal uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, services improvement, contact, and research.

## COOKIES

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to login to the Listal service, we use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site

## DATA STORAGE

Listal uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Listal.

## DISCLOSURE

  * Listal may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](https://www.listal.com/help/tos).

## CHANGES

Listal may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your Listal account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## ADVERTISING

We use third party advertisements on listal.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google�s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (�interest based targeting�). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses �non personally identifiable information�. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to tom at listal.com
